<caption>
    <text type="en">

        <p>As it turns out, the American public isn't fooled by Obama's and Pelosi's strong-arm tactics, according to a recent Zogby International/O'Leary Report Poll. (The poll surveyed 3,544 voters, was conducted October 23-26, and has a margin of error of 1.7 percentage points.) The poll asked:</p>
        
        <p>House Speaker Nancy Pelosi recently condemned the health insurance industry for releasing an unflattering analysis on the Obama administration's proposal to create a government-run "public option" health insurance plan. Pelosi also threatened to revoke the industry's anti-trust exemption which has been in place since 1945. Do you agree or disagree that Pelosi is using the power of congress to try to limit the free speech of private corporations?</p>
        
        <p>A majority of American voters (53 percent) agree that Pelosi is trying to use the power of congress to limit the free speech of private industry. Only 39 percent disagree. Furthermore, 55 percent of Independent voters also agree, while just 39 percent disagree. Majorities of Hispanic voters (52 percent), union members (51 percent), and small business owners (58 percent) agree as well.  </p>
    </text>

    <text lang="he">
           <p>
                  כפי שהתברר, הציבור האמריקני אינו שולל על ידי אובמה ו פלוסי של טקטיקות זרוע חזקה, על פי הבינלאומי     
                       האחרונות / אולירי דווח על סקר. (הסקר נסקרו 3,544 מצביעים, נערכה אוקטובר 23-26, ויש לו טעות הדגימה של 1.7 נקודות אחוז.) הסקר שאל:
           </p>

           <p>
                  יו"ר בית הנבחרים ננסי פלוסי גינו לאחרונה את תעשיית ביטוח בריאות עבור שחרור ניתוח מחמיאים על ההצעה להקים ממשלת ממשל אובמה וברח "אפשרות הציבור" תוכנית ביטוח בריאות. פלוסי גם איימו לבטל את התעשייה של אנטי פטור אמון אשר עברו במקום מאז 1945. האם אתה מסכים או לא מסכים כי פלוסי היא באמצעות כוחו של הקונגרס כדי לנסות להגביל 
את חופש הביטוי של תאגידים פרטיים?
            </p>


             <p>
                   רוב הבוחרים האמריקני (53 אחוז) מסכימים כי פלוסי מנסה להשתמש בכוחה של הקונגרס להגביל את חופש הביטוי של התעשייה הפרטית. רק 39 אחוזים מסכימים. יתרה מזאת, 55 אחוזים ממצביעי עצמאי גם מסכים, ואילו רק 39 אחוזים מסכימים. רוב המצביעים היספני (52 אחוז), חברי האיגוד (51 אחוזים), ועל בעלי עסקים קטנים (58 אחוז) מסכים גם.
             </p>

    </text>
  
</caption>
